According to the Solar Energy Industries Association, the number of solar panels installed has grown rapidly in the past decade, and it has to grow even faster to meet climate goals.
据太阳能产业协会称，过去十年里，已安装的太阳能电池板数量增长迅速，而要实现气候目标，增长速度还必须更快。
But all of that growth will take up a lot of space, and though more and more people accept the concept of solar energy, few like large solar panels to be installed near them.
但所有这些增长都会占用大量空间；而且，尽管越来越多的人接受了太阳能这一理念，却很少有人愿意自家附近装上大型太阳能电池板。
Solar developers want to put up panels as quickly and cheaply as possible, so they haven’t given much thought to what they put under them.
太阳能开发商希望尽可能快速、低成本地架设电池板，因此一直没怎么考虑在电池板下面放些什么。
Often, they’ll end up filling the area with small stones and using chemicals to control weeds.
他们最后往往会在这片区域铺满小石子，并使用化学药剂来控制杂草。
The result is that many communities, especially in farming regions, see solar farms as destroyers of the soil.
结果，许多社区，尤其是农业地区的社区，都把太阳能电站看作土壤的破坏者。
“Solar projects need to be good neighbors,” says Jordan Macknick, the head of the Innovative Site Preparation and Impact Reductions on the Environment (InSPIRE) project.
“创新场地准备与降低环境影响”（InSPIRE）项目负责人乔丹·麦克尼克说：“太阳能项目需要做个好邻居。”
“They need to be protectors of the land and contribute to the agricultural economy.”
“它们需要成为土地的保护者，并为农业经济做出贡献。”
InSPIRE is investigating practical approaches to “low-impact” solar development, which focuses on establishing and operating solar farms in a way that is kinder to the land.
InSPIRE 项目正在研究实现“低影响”太阳能开发的可行方法，这种开发注重以对土地更友好的方式建设和运营太阳能电站。
One of the easiest low-impact solar strategies is providing habitat for pollinators.
最简单的低影响太阳能策略之一，就是为传粉昆虫提供栖息地。
Habitat loss, pesticide use, and climate change have caused dramatic declines in pollinator populations over the past couple of decades, which has damaged the U.S. agricultural economy.
过去二十来年里，栖息地丧失、农药使用和气候变化导致传粉昆虫数量急剧下降，这已经损害了美国的农业经济。
Over 28 states have passed laws related to pollinator habitat protection and pesticide use.
已有超过28个州通过了与传粉昆虫栖息地保护和农药使用相关的法律。
Conservation organizations put out pollinator-friendliness guidelines for home gardens, businesses, schools, cities—and now there are guidelines for solar farms.
各类自然保护组织针对家庭花园、企业、学校和城市发布了如何善待传粉昆虫的指南，如今也有了针对太阳能电站的同类指南。
Over the past few years, many solar farm developers have transformed the space under their solar panels into a shelter for various kinds of pollinators, resulting in soil improvement and carbon reduction.
过去几年里，许多太阳能电站开发商已把电池板下方的空间改造成各类传粉昆虫的庇护所，从而改善了土壤，减少了碳排放。
“These pollinator-friendly solar farms can have a valuable impact on everything that’s going on in the landscape,” says Macknick.
“这些对传粉昆虫友好的太阳能电站，能给这一带土地上正在发生的一切带来非常有益的影响，”麦克尼克说。